streetlife.com 2014-07-02

# Streetlife | Privacy Policy

###  The following sets out Streetlife's Privacy policy and procedures on the collection, use and disclosure of your information. 

Streetlife is a registered data controller - registration Z2095612. Streetlife receives your information through our various websites, SMS, APIs, services and third-parties ("Services"). 

When using any of our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. 

Irrespective of which country that you reside in or create information from, your information may be used by Streetlife in the United Kingdom or any other country where Streetlife operates. 

If you are under age 18, please do not attempt to register for Streetlife or provide any personal information about yourself to us. If we learn that we have collected personal information from a person under age 18, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from a person under age 18, please contact us. 

### Information Collected Upon Registration

When you create or reconfigure a Streetlife account, you provide some personal information, such as your name, username, and postal and email addresses. 

### Sensitive Information Collected Upon Registration

When you create or reconfigure a Streetlife account, you provide some sensitive personal information, such as a password, and credit card details. Streetlife does not store your password in a format where it can ever be accessed or retrieved by our staff or agents. Streetlife does not store your credit card details. These details are used only for address verification, and never stored in any of our systems, or in our log data. 

### Log Data

Our servers automatically record information ("Log Data") created by your use of the Services. Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, the referring domain, pages visited, and search terms. Other actions, such as interactions with advertisements, may also be included in Log Data.

### Cookies

Like many websites, we use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve our Services. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer's hard disk. Streetlife may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our Services, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our Services, and to improve our Services. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. 

### User communications

When you send emails or other communications to Streetlife, we may retain those communications in order to process your enquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 

### Links

Streetlife may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our search technology, customised content and advertising. 

### Other sites

This Privacy Policy applies to Streetlife's services only. We do not exercise control over the sites displayed as search results, sites that include Streetlife applications, products or services or links from within our various services. These other sites may page their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. 

Streetlife processes personal information on our servers in the United Kingdom and in other countries. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country. We may process personal information to provide our own services. In some cases, we may process personal information on behalf of and according to the instructions of a third party, such as our advertising partners. 

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent and we expect that the majority of such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes). Each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.
